I have no degree.
I used to work in door-to-door sales.
And when you see this framework,
you'll be wondering one thing:
Why did this guy
teach us all this for free?
If you've watched any of my videos before,
you'll know
I talk about a four-stage sales system.
Let's get into stage number one, socials,
social media.
The easiest way we can break this up
is to short and longs.
Short, let's say up to three minutes.
Longs, something over three minutes.
If every time you talk about a subject,
you find yourself doing three, four, five
minutes about it,
it's probably better off on YouTube.
Our first consideration between the two of
these is how people are going to access
them. On shorts,
they're going to be served it.
On longs,
they're going to have to click on it.
Over the last few years,
we've seen something happen called the
TikTokification of
social media. For so long,
we would only see someone's content if we
followed them. But now
that model has changed massively.
TikTok started by showing people content
they'd be interested in, not the creators
they followed.
We're now seeing this follow suit with
Reels on Instagram.
Same thing's happened on LinkedIn,
Facebook, even YouTube Shorts.
So suddenly,
if you're making short-form content,
it's not the packaging, it's not
how many followers you've got,
it's the very first thing you do in
that video
that's going to determine whether
or not someone watches it or stays.
So the first thing we need to understand
is human behavior.
For most of you, when is it
that you watch shorts?
When is it that you do the majority of
your scrolling?
I don't know about you, but for me,
it's when I'm in bed at night.
And we scroll, we scroll, we scroll,
we scroll, we scroll.
On average,
we probably give a video about two
seconds, so we need to work on our
hooks.
The hooks are going to be the first thing
we say in a video.
Even before we hit record on this video
today, I took 10,
15 seconds to think about
what was the first thing I
was going to say in
that video so you can ensure that
you're watching the right video. There
are different types of hooks. Visual.
This wobbly thing here of fat,
I've used before to represent body fat.
I had really good success in short-form
content by showing people this.
This is five pounds of body fat.
To lose this amount of weight, mah, mah,
mah, mah,
mah. We have a statement hook.
A statement hook might begin by saying,
"This has
got 120 milligrams of caffeine in it" and,
"Did you know?" Often, visual
hooks and statement hooks
are put together. This
is 200 calories of Skittles.
Then we have a preview hook,
often done in trailers
or showing things that are
coming up in the video. This
is why I really don't like channel
trailers where they
put their logo and a bit of sound because
you're just killing the beginning of
that. But we don't really see
that in short-form content that much.
Your best one's going to be visual hooks,
statement hooks, and preview hooks.
I nearly forgot question hooks.
Probably the best ones.
How many Skittles would I need to eat to
gain a pound of body fat?
How many miles are there between the world
and the moon? I don't know.
It's worth noting that these hooks
are also needed in long-form
content,
but they're much more important in
short-form content because the person
needs to make the decision whether
or not they're going to watch your video.
So when we come over from shorts to longs,
the first thing we need to look at is
packaging. And your packaging
is going to be your title
and thumbnail because the
main place you're going to put this
is YouTube.
A title and thumbnail
is what's going to cause inquisit in
that person.
So the two things they need to have in
their mind, how or why.
If someone sees your title
and thumbnail and thinks these
are those two things, the
chances of them clicking
are going to be much higher.
However, just because
that person has clicked,
like you have clicked on this,
it doesn't mean you're out of the woods.
You still now have to retain that person.
And the two ways you're going to do this,
pay off the title and thumbnail and the
intro.
I did a video the other day where I make
$5,337 a day, and I teach
people how I did it.
But I actually had to pay that off.
So that people didn't know it
was a random number,
I bring up the information on my
Stripe account so I can actually show
people, and then I've shown them it's the
last 90 days,
so you have the revenue divided by 90.
I had to pay off
that exact number because some people
would've seen that title and
thumbnail and gone,
"Why such a specific number?"
And they get that payoff straight
away. Then they realize what the video
is about.
If I never mentioned
or never spoke about that,
they would think I was just baiting
them. Think. Great language, James.
Now, your introduction
is a very important thing in long and in
short,
but your introduction also needs to make
people feel
sure that they're watching the right
video.
So again, whatever your video is about,
let's say it's about the squat.
You need people to very early on
understand what's to come.
Are you squatting correctly?
Are you squatting to enough depth?
Should you be wearing lifting shoes?
And what counts as parallel?
Suddenly,
I've asked all these questions without
even giving people the answers,
but they now know what they're going to
get if they stick with this video.
And the next effect,
I call it letting the shoulders down.
When people click on your video,
if they don't follow you, they hate you,
and they
are ready to leave at any given point.
But if you can give them good packaging,
a good intro, and pay off the title and
thumbnail,
you can let their shoulders to drop.
And if their shoulders drop,
they might even put their phone down.
They might even be cooking dinner.
They might even be listening to it in the
background when they're folding clothes
in their room. And when you can do that,
you're going to get some retention.
Now, after these two things,
we're going to meet in the middle a little
bit.
We're going to want good pacing.
Highly recommend pattern interrupt.
Even me switching from front to back
camera to this one over here, or even
that one
then, all forms of pattern interrupt.
Even if I go from talking here to talking
here with a jump cut, just giving you
that little change of scenery
and a little different effect on natural
lighting is
going to make all the difference.
Our eyes get very bored.
You'll even notice
that some YouTube channels at the moment
show footage of video
games being played whilst they're making
their point.
Get to the point that you want to make.
With these, in long
and short-form content, imagine this
is like a
boxing combination,
especially in short-form content.
In boxing,
you want to throw your combination.
You want to get in, then get out.
You want to start from range where you're
safe,
get in,
left, right, good night, get out.
With content,
there should be the same amount of
urgency to get in, make the point,
get out.
Don't waffle, don't ramble,
don't be asking for a call to action too
soon.
Just make the point you want to make
and get out.
With YouTube, as long as you
are not boring,
they will continue to watch.
When it comes to having an outro,
a call to action, there
is a golden rule you must
pay attention to,
and we call this the rule of goodwill.
On social media,
your objective in the onset
is to accrue goodwill.
It is to give people little moments where
they go, "Oh, never really thought of
that before. Oh, never really noticed
that before." And if you do that enough
times,
you're going to accrue a currency of
goodwill, which is way better than
money.
Because if you just do your first video,
"Oh, guys, and comment the word
punch,
and I'll send you a boxing breakdown."
They're like, "Who are you, mate?
Fuck off." In the onset, even
if it takes three to six months, try
and accrue as
much goodwill as you can with strangers on
the internet, so that when you first ask
for their email address
or ask them to go to a landing page
or ask them to do
whatever, they will do it.
Which brings me on to stage two of our
funnel, the
squeeze.
Some people call this a lead magnet.
I'm just going to go through some of the
things that are imperative that you
understand in this day and age.
Once you've accrued enough goodwill, it
is time to
get someone's email address. It
is time to take this conversation away
from the
dance floor to a proper place. It
is time to leave that person alone on the
dance floor and wait till they get home on
Monday and message them to say, "Would
you like to go for a drink?" My favorite
platforms for this are AWeber,
Klaviyo, and SendGrid. In that order.
These are the places.
These create all the email addresses for
you.
Then to get the email addresses on here,
you're going to need a squeeze page.
For any of you watching this, there
is a link in description that you can
look at,
'30 Days in 30 Ways.' You can feel free to
copy mine.
To take someone's email address,
we need to give them something of value.
A principle for this,
what's in it for me with him?
So Declan here, if he
was to do a squeeze page,
he could do something like,
"Over the next 11 days,
I'm going to show you how to color grade
your footage from
log to make it look the best it's ever
been." "Over the next 14 days, we're going
to go through different lens focal
lengths,
and I'm going to show you footage and
photos so you can understand what the
difference is between a 24 mil, a
50 mil, and an 80 mil,
and you can understand the exact settings
you need to be
using those millimeters in." Another one
could be, "Over the next 30 days, each
day,
I'm going to be giving you an editing hack
that you can use in DaVinci Pro to
make your processes of editing not only
easier, but more seamless, and to
ensure that anyone
that ever works with you will never want
you to leave." Then
all Declan's got to do
is write up those sequences as an email
autoresponder. Writes email one, 24 hours.
Write email two, 24 hours.
Writes email three, wait 24 hours.
And the best bit is,
Declan only needs to really write three of
these emails, and
he can start promoting people to sign up.
As long as he remains a day ahead,
they will keep getting the autoresponder.
Now, depending on the length
that you want to go with,
you're in charge, you're the
boss, I don't tell you what to do.
You could send the first few without a
call to
action. Then ultimately,
you've not only accrued goodwill on social
media in stage
one,
you're now starting to accrue goodwill in
stage two, the email marketing
funnel.
They're getting your emails every day.
They're going, "Oh, I cannot believe this.
I cannot believe
that every day I'm getting these nuggets.
How am I getting this for free?" They're
then starting to implement the things that
you're telling them about on email
marketing,
and they're starting to have a real
impact on their business.
The stuff you put on their social media at
first is now
starting to pay off. Now, the things
that you're giving them in email, they're
starting to implement.
They're quite literally getting to the
point now where
they're thinking,
"How do I do business with this guy?"
There's going to be a
certain amount of emails
that you're going to have to do before
they consider doing
business with you.
The link in the description,
I've told people on average,
between days 19 and 21,
people end up buying into my business
mentorship. Cool. So then from here,
we have the email marketing campaign.
Some people will never bite,
but then at the end of the responder,
you could do
a discount,
you could do a lower ticket offer,
or just leave them there.
Another thing you might want to do instead
is clean.
So every once in a while, with your list,
if they haven't clicked on your offer or
they haven't been opening your emails,
feel free to delete them because you are
paying for that. You can leave,
you can clean.
The benefits with leaving someone on your
email list is they just might not be
right for what you're doing,
and in a few months' time, they might be.
I'm sure there are people on my email list
that never, ever, ever joined my PT
program,
but the second I launched the world's
first productivity drink,
they bought a case. They went,
"Do you know what, James?
I'm in better shape than you.
I never really need your program, but
when you bring
the drink out,
I'll support you." You never know,
Declan could bring out a book
soon. When he brings out the book,
they go, "Hey, bro,
I wasn't interested in your
online course. I'm a bit of a technophobe,
but I'll buy your book." And some people
buy from you,
not even just because they need the thing.
They do it as a token of appreciation.
Shaun Casey,
people bought his recipe books.
For the recipes? No. They see a young,
ambitious guy doing his thing.
They go, "Do you know what, Shaun?
Do you know what, Shaun?
I'll buy your recipe book because you're a
good lad and you've been putting out
free content for us over the years.
So my way of showing you an appreciation
is I'll get your recipe book." Did they
cook any recipes? Did they fuck? Now,
how do you get good at writing emails?
Good question. Well,
you write more of them.
Same way that if you want to get good at
chin-ups, you do more chin-ups.
Declan, do you do a lot of chin-ups?
Show them. Move the barbell.
Chin-ups or pull-ups? Chin-ups
or pull-ups. We'll go pull-ups.
We'll go pull-ups.
Oh, a bit of chalk, is it?
What's your advice to someone
that wants to get good at pull-ups?
Do weighted pull-ups for less reps. Okay.
Can you actually just answer
that question?
You can keep this in the edit.
Can you just say, "Do more pull-ups"?
Sorry?
[laughs] Can you answer my question where
I said- Yeah.
So if you want to do more pull-ups,
do less reps, but weighted.
The answer I wanted was do more pull-ups,
but that's fine.
What I was trying to get to, my point
is that if you want to get good at
pull-ups,
do more. Do more pull-ups. Yeah,
I'll tell you- Yeah. No, that's fine.
It's all right.
Every time you write an email marketing
email, you are working that
muscle in your mind
that has to be creative,
has to come up with ideas, and we're
going to go on a quick tangent. Okay.
The email marketing thing
is split into two.
Let's say the two genres of email
marketing can be broadcast and
autoresponder. So if you
were going to set up an email chain of 20,
30, 40 emails in a row that people
are going to get, that's going to be an
autoresponder.
You're going to pre-write them.
They're going to be there.
So if you do click the link in my bio
and join that email sequence, I've already
written those.
I wrote those about six months ago.
You're going to get them anyway.
But I do broadcast on top of that.
So the autoresponders
are going to be thought
out. They're going to be well-written.
They're going to be strategic,
and they're probably going to be a little
bit bland
because the proposition for this is value.
Now,
a broadcast is what you send on top of
that.
So once someone joins your email list,
these ones are automated.
But the broadcast is, let's say,
Black Friday.
Your Black Friday offer isn't going to be
in your autoresponder because unless
someone joins at a particular time of the
year, that's just not going to be there.
But when you broadcast on top, this
is where we want to bring in stories.
This is when we want to bring in
time-sensitive issues.
So if you've got an interesting story,
I always talk about the time
that I went to
LA and I got a laundry bill. Well,
actually, I went to LA.
We're leaving the hotel the next day.
I call them up and say,
"Can we do the laundry?
I want it tomorrow." I didn't look at the
pricing.
The next day, they said it
was going to be in the room by 9:00 AM.
At 9:30, I call them up and I go, "Look,
where's my laundry?
You said it was going to be here.
It's not here." They said, "Sir,
check your
wardrobe." Suddenly, I knew.
I knew at that moment.
See what I'm doing here?
I'm telling the story. At this moment,
I was like, "If it's in my wardrobe,
this is
going to be some expensive laundry." It
was. It was $550 US.
It would've been cheaper to fly my mum
from London to LA to get her to do
my laundry and fly her back than it
would've been for that.
That made a good story because then in
that email, I said,
"The only way you could
have a worse day than me is
if you don't join my program." So
autoresponders, a bit
more serious. For the broadcasts, stories,
same time sensitive.
Look, back in the day, there
were times I prematurely ejaculated on a
first date.
I put it in a broadcast. This
is your cake.
These are your sprinkles
that go on top of it.
Broadcasts, stories, funny things
that have happened.
Share it in real time so
that one day someone will fist bump you on
the street and
go, "Oh, man," or, "Oh, lady,
that story you told about
that first date from
Hinge was hilarious.
Thank you so much." There
are so many people that back in the
day read my emails just because they
wanted to be entertained,
and there comes a
day,
there comes a day where their jeans don't
button up and they go, "You got me.
You got me." Because no one's mental
enough to try and sell to someone 10
months.
Okay, let's get to stage three, shall we?
Come on, James.
So we've got the email address.
You're sending fire.
If in the autoresponder,
give people a bit of breathing room, okay?
Give people a bit of breathing room.
Maybe don't have a call to action for the
first few, then start hammering them
because you're not a charity.
But there comes a time
that eventually someone's
going to click on that link. Where's
that link going to take them?
We now reach stage three,
the landing page Now some people
get this confused with a squeeze page.
I'm going to make it very,
very easy for people to understand.
Squeeze page, one objective. What's that,
Declan? Get the email address.
Cool. Landing page, one objective.
Get people to buy a product.
Get people to buy the product.
Now,
even if they don't end up buying your
product, that
is okay.
We kind of want them perusing the menu.
And I've said this a lot of times before,
the landing page is like someone walking
past your restaurant.
It's us showing them the menu.
You don't just have what it
is on the menu. You make it sexy.
And for the entrees,
we have the quesadilla.
You don't just say quesadilla.
You say,
"We've got some of the finest cheese mixed
with some of the tomato pico de
gallo." You make it sexy.
You do the same here.
You overpromise, you overdeliver. Now,
I won't go into this in too much detail.
We need what it is, why they need it,
what they get, why to trust you, how
to pay, Stripe, why to trust you,
and a money-back guarantee.
These will be case dependent on what you
want.
And again,
I've said this a million times before.
Let's make this look real sexy.
Video sales letter. Video sales letter
is a video that you're going to put on
that
page. And real simply,
it's not overly edited.
A bit like this video.
It's kind of chilled. Imagine this
is a video sales letter. Hi, guys.
Welcome to my business mentorship page.
My business mentorship
is a video module course where I break
down all of the
lessons that you need to understand from
email marketing, squeeze pages, landing
pages, how to set all your pricing,
how to differentiate yourself, how to make
content on social media.
It's not just that.
You get access to a Discord community
where I'm in there every day helping you,
giving you critique on your videos.
The reason you need this
is you need someone to support you
and to give you
feedback on the things you're doing.
The people in your gym just aren't going
to be able to do that, and you're probably
going to need someone in your life that's
done the things that you want to do in
your life. Why to trust me?
Because there are testimonials of some of
the coaches
that I've had beneath. If you join today,
you'll get access to all the other
courses. You see what I mean.
It's just candid. It's just chatting.
It's just getting to know
that person so that they know it's not a
scam.
As far as software for these pages,
I do not get paid to say
this.
I think Leadpages do the nicest looking
pages.
This is your menu. Some people try
and host their landing page on shitty
websites like Wix and Squarespace,
or even try and host it with an email
marketing
platform.
You wouldn't do a menu to a restaurant
and put it on shitty paper, or do
it in Times New Roman, would you?
You wouldn't skimp on
that bit because you've
built the building. You've got the chefs.
You've built the kitchen.
You've got the tables and chairs,
and you clean the knives and the forks,
and you
mop the floor.
Then you decide to skimp at the menu,
the one thing that's going to
stop people from ordering and paying
and giving you money.
Do you understand how crazy that is?
So when I come across businesses
that do everything right,
they've got the degree,
they've done the S&C qualification,
they've got their fucking whatever it
is in
osteopath kinesiology.
They've got a shit landing page,
and it creates a bottleneck
for everything that they do because it
just looks like shit.
Now, some golden rules, which again,
not everyone's going to agree with me on.
Fuck sales calls unless you're really
desperate.
If you're really desperate
and you're like, "I need two clients
or you're going to
fucking go under," don't do it.
If someone says they want a sales call,
do you
offer a money-back guarantee for a month.
Go, "Look,
I'd love to jump on a call with you,
but I'm a busy professional.
I've got loads of clients in here
that I'm servicing.
It's not fair for me to give you an hour
when I've got people that are paying me
that need that hour." Why someone needs a
sales call after a money-back guarantee,
I just don't know. I just don't know.
Pricing.
I know a lot of you at the moment
are in this position where you're like,
"Oh, and
pay six months up front
and get a discount.
And if you do three months up front."
People are fucking broke right now.
Interest rates are high to cause a problem
to get people to stop spending money.
Quite literally, to deal with inflation,
the whole world is stopping people from
spending loads of money. And now you,
so many of you, have made it a goddamn
prerequisite that someone needs to have
£500 or $1,000 to do business with you.
Make it as easy as possible.
If you can offer weekly pricing,
it's all the same to
you.
Whether you get paid four times a month
or four times that amount once a month
or 12 times that amount every 90 days,
it doesn't matter to you that much, but to
them, it matters a lot. To some people,
spending $500 takes
them between having no money
and being able to survive the month.
Plus, some people,
if you give them the opportunity to train
for a week or two
weeks, they'll go, "Hey, come on, man.
It's 60 bucks.
It's 60 bucks, man.
I'll try him out for a week," or,
"I'll try her out for a
week." They get in and go, "Wow,
I get all this for 60 bucks?
I'm never leaving." But you guys,
the higher you put your price point,
and I'm
not asking you to be cheaper,
I'm asking for you lot to make it easier.
If you're a personal trainer or a physio,
you're not like, "Oh, you got to pay me
for three months in advance." Come in,
let me treat you, get out.
Pay me weekly, pay me however you like.
Just say to people,
"I appreciate the economic climate
is tough.
Pay me how you like." Those of you
that are like, "Oh, I need a
three-month commitment," it just makes you
seem insecure.
You don't need commitments from people
unless you're shit, because
if you're really
good, people are never leaving.
The second you're like,
"You need a three-month
commitment up front," it just makes me
feel like you're broke and you need the
money, which is not what we want.
A friend of mine yesterday tells me,
"Declan," good-looking mate,
one of my best-looking mates says to me,
in Bondi, he
told a girl he wanted a relationship.
She called it off two days later.
I said, "Of course.
You said you wanted a relationship."
That's the golden rule.
You never say what you want.
If he had just been chill,
she probably would have
tried to lock him down,
and he could have played it off,
and they could have
settled into a relationship.
The second you try too hard,
people don't like it.
As a man on a night out, not me
and Declan because we're in happy
relationships,
all you want to do is take a girl home
and sleep with her.
But if she was to say, "Take me home
and let me sleep with you," you're like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on?" People read people very
well. Don't try too hard.
Don't try locking them in. Just be like,
"Yeah, if you want to train with me,
that's okay.
Here's the price." Three-month commitment,
don't need it.
"Oh,
why is that?" Because I'm great at my job,
and you give me a week, you're
never leaving.
For my online coaching platform,
you get a seven-day free
trial and a two-week money-back guarantee
on top of that. Why?
Because it's good.
And by removing all the barriers we can,
people that are like,
"I have no interest in joining.
I'm just going to check it out," become
lifelong
bloody clients.
We're just going to quickly look into the
trickle effect, which is
a term I just made up.
You get 1,000 people to follow you on
social media.
20% is a golden rule.
Give me 200 people you want in emails.
If you are not getting 20% of that 1,000,
you're not squeezing people hard enough.
Out of those, let's say 25%
are going to go to your landing page,
which is going to
be 50 people. Out of 50 people
that land on your landing page,
you might get one
client. So if you want five clients,
you're going to need 5,000 views.
You're going to need 1,000 emails.
This funnel, over time,
only becomes more narrow and more
efficient because you get better at making
content, you get better at writing
emails,
you perfect your landing page over time,
and your business builds a better
reputation. The reality is in the onset,
your funnel looks like this.
It's going to be so difficult to even get
10%.
And then out of that, people
that go to your landing page,
it's going to be like
this. And then out of this,
you probably get 0.5 clients.
And it'll be frustrating,
and you'll think
that everything you're doing is shit,
but just keep in mind, I promise you,
as you keep hustling, your client
reputation, emails, content,
you're just going to become a killer.
Funnels can only get thinner Can only
get thinner now, because I teach you.
Cor,
I hope that doesn't get copyright struck.
So understand, in the onset,
a bit like being a white belt in jujitsu,
you are so
shit, but as you get better,
and you become more efficient in every
part of your
game, from guard, guard retention,
passing, takedowns, soon you end up as a
black belt. When you start jujitsu,
the amount of people that sub you
is everyone.
And then suddenly it's 90% of people,
then it's 80% of people.
Then before you know it,
you're a black belt
and you haven't been tapped out in
three months.
It's the same for content creation.
It's the same for all of these processes
that I'm teaching you about now.
Stage four, the sale.
Something we need to talk about.
I have a golden rule in marketing.
If you're doing face-to-face business,
or if
you're doing online, there
is only a finite amount of sessions
or people that you
can work with. So let's map it out.
Let's imagine a spectrum.
Let's say this is the optimal amount of
clients that you want to work with. Cool.
Let's call this max. If you're here,
you need to market harder. How do I know?
Because you're not full. If you're here,
you need to market harder.
And if you're at maximum capacity,
you need to increase your rates.
Why do you need to increase your rates?
Because you're full.
This means you are too cheap.
How do I know?
Because you wouldn't be full unless you
were too cheap.
So many of us get to this point here
thinking this is cool because this means
more
money, when the reality
is the further you go here, the worse your
level of service gets.
And going here jeopardizes
all of these, because you all know
if you stretch yourself too thin,
you're going
to reduce your level of quality.
Not only that,
if you're doing too much with the
people that pay you,
you're not going to have the energy to do
the content and the
things you need to get the people
that haven't paid you yet.
So we never want to take on too many
people.
Now, if you put your rates up,
something could happen.
You could end up well below capacity
again.
Now,
this looks very worrying from the outset,
but let's make this clear.
If you increase your rates by 10% or 15%,
which is completely normal, here
you are earning more money than you did
here in the red before.
You are better off having less clients pay
you more, than too many
clients paying you the same rate.
And it's a lot more money in comparison
when I
teach you this one thing. And this
is how you're going to get the confidence
to put
your rates up.
Let's imagine a client pays you this
amount.
This bit here is going to be costs.
Even me making this video, this camera,
that camera, that guy,
this fucking studio, are costs.
Then I've got tax. These aren't two sides.
Then here, let's say take-home.
If I want to give someone a discount,
I would have
to say I take 10% off my costs.
My tax reduces maybe a tiny bit.
My costs remain the same.
I'm really just eating into my flipping
take-home.
Whereas if you increase the amount
that you're charging someone,
your tax may be
a couple of percent, your costs
are not going to change.
Whenever you put your rates up, it
is just extra money in your pocket.
The only place your prices can ever go
is up.
Now,
the only way you can put your rates up
is through demand.
The best lesson I can ever give you
is it's not the amount of degrees you got,
it's
not where you went to uni,
it's not how good looking you are,
it's not the
socioeconomic state of the country,
it's not who's the president of the United
States,
it's not what's happening with Bitcoin
prices.
The thing that determines how much you
charge is the demand for your
services. The more people
that want what it is to sell, the more you
can charge for it. It's the reason
that Rolex can charge £6,000 for a
watch. It's the reason
that Ferrari can charge half a million
pounds for a car.
Ferrari and Porsche don't even advertise.
Well, I've never seen an advert for it.
Because they have such demand for their
services.
And the way that you're going to create
adamant demand for your services is using
social media, making good content
that resonates with people where you can
retain
them. You can talk about subjects
that solve their problems.
You can then get people's email addresses
from them.
You can give them a lot of value
and a bit of entertainment.
You can send people to a well-curated
landing page where they can peruse the
menu.
Remember, we don't want to be too pushy.
Like a restaurant owner, "Hey brother,
come in, check out the menu.
Let me know if there's any questions."
Not, "Hey, you want to come eat in my
restaurant?
Let's jump on a call for 45 minutes
and let's talk about it, and maybe
you could give me a three-month commitment
where you come to my..." No. Be relaxed.
Be chilled. "There's everything.
Let me know if you have any questions."
Or, "Is there anything you can do on
price?" "Sorry, I've got staff,
I've got a lovely restaurant."
If someone wants a
discount in your restaurant,
go eat somewhere else, mate.
And again,
if someone's unsure about using your
services, send them somewhere else.
Send them somewhere else.
Here's the thing, right.
Alex Hormozi said this.
It's probably the only thing
that really resonated that he said.
He goes,
"People need to be reminded more than they
need to be taught." This, for
some of you,
you know most of this already.
You need to be reminded of this,
not taught this.
You already know what you should be doing,
you just haven't been doing it.
And again, think about this.
I know a lot of you are fitness people.
Creatine.
You take it, makes you 8% stronger,
gives you 3% more muscle mass.
But you take it because
that performance enhancement of only 8%
is worth it to you.
You take it every day,
you do it every day.
Getting this right, even
if it only gave you an 8% gain on what you
were doing,
that is a staggering amount of money over
months and years.
That's how you should see me.
Creatine gains for your business.
Am I going to four-fold the revenue your
business makes in a year? No.
But if you get these processes right,
you might see a nice 8% to 10%
improvement.
And that,
as a return on investment of what my
course is, is a flipping bargain.
So I'll put a link to the 30-day
autoresponder in the description.
I'll also put a link in there for my
business course if you want to work with
me,
and YouTube recommends
that you should watch this video of mine.
And as we've said before, YouTube
is very smart,
so if YouTube thinks you need to
watch it, I think you should watch it.